fap-nation.com 2019-05-21

# Privacy Policy | FAP-Nation

## **1\. Welcome to our Privacy Policy**

It is FAP-Nation’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to [www.fap-nation.com](https://fap-nation.com/) (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, “our”, FAP-Nation, website or “www.fap-nation.com”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the website. We have adopted this privacy policy to explain what information may be collected on our website, how we use this information and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This privacy policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to collection of information from other sources.

This privacy policy, together with the [Terms of Servise](https://fap-nation.com/terms-of-service/) and [Disclaimer](https://fap-nation.com/disclaimer/) published on our website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our website. Depending on your activities when visiting FAP-Nation, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.

## **2\. Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, FAP-Nation collects non-personally identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, device, language preference, referring site, OS and the date and time of each visitor request. FAP-Nation’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how FAP-Nation’s visitors use its website and maintain our security standards. From time to time, FAP-Nation may release non-personally identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

FAP-Nation also collects potentially personally identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for users leaving comments and ratings on posts. FAP-Nation only discloses IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally identifying information as described below.

## **3\. Gathering of Personally Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to FAP-Nation choose to interact with the website in ways that require FAP-Nation to gather personally identifying information. The amount and type of information that FAP-Nation gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who leave a comment to provide a nickname and email address if they choose to do so.

## **4\. Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## **5\. Advertisements**

Advertisements appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners who may set cookies. These cookies allow the advertisement delivery server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement and to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows advertisement networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by FAP-Nation and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## **6\. Links to External Websites**

Our Service may contain links to external websites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website. We strongly advise you to review the privacy policy and terms and conditions of every website you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party websites, products or services.

## **7\. Protection of Certain Personally Identifying Information**

FAP-Nation discloses potentially personally identifying information only to those of its employees, team members, partners, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on FAP-Nation’s behalf or to provide services available at FAP-Nation’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, team members, partners, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country. By using FAP-Nation’s website you consent to the transfer of such information to them. FAP-Nation will not rent or sell potentially personally identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, team members, partners, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above. FAP-Nation discloses potentially personally identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request issued by the officials of the websites local country or when FAP-Nation believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of FAP-Nation, third parties or the public at large.

If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. FAP-Nation takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally identifying information.

## **8\. Aggregated Statistics**

FAP-Nation may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. FAP-Nation may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, FAP-Nation does not disclose your potentially personally identifying information.

## **9\. Cookies**

To enrich and perfect your online experience, FAP-Nation uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. FAP-Nation uses cookies to identify and track visitors, their usage of the website and their website preferences. FAP-Nation visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using FAP-Nation’s website, with the drawback that certain features of FAP-Nation’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to FAP-Nation’s use of cookies. Please, inform yourself more in depth about the use of cookies and the associated practices.

## **10\. Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, FAP-Nation may change its privacy policy from time to time and in FAP-Nation’s sole discretion. FAP-Nation encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its privacy policy. Your continued use of the website after any change in this privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
